http://www.minimus.biz/privacy.aspx

Sugar Free Food
Welcome to our specialty food and beverage aisles! Here we have a large selection of gourmet & imported foods and diet specific items.
Skin Protection
Welcome to the Personal Health and first aid aisles at Minimus.biz. Here you will find travel-sized and individual sized versions of your over the counter medications, first aid products, and more.
Household
Household
Bathroom Supplies
Cleaning Supplies
Household Kits
Laundry & Garment Care
Mini Office Supplies
Baby & Toddler
Customer Service
Contact UsTerms and ConditionsFAQSpecial ServicesPrivacy PolicyReturn RequestSite Map
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting our web site.
Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis.
Please note that the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites using any of the hyperlinks on our site, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.Information
Minimus is the sole owner of the information collected on this website. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors.
Minimus does not target registration to, or knowingly collect information directly from, anyone under 13 years of age. Additionally, Minimus will never distribute any personally identifiable information concerning any minor, regardless of the source from which it was obtained.
If you have any questions regarding any aspect of our Privacy Policy or would like to remove any information you believe was inadvertently collected directly from a child less than thirteen years of age, please email us at
.
Account RegistrationOur website allows you the option of registering for an account with us.
This is an optional feature, you are not required to register for an account in order to make purchases from our site.
This information is used to contact you regarding your order and any additional information you may have requested from us.
Additionally, your account access will allow you to check your order information online as well as use other account-related services.OrdersWe request information from you on our order form. Here you must provide contact information (like name, shipping address, email) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with you.Cookies & IP Addresses
A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing information about you. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our website. Once you close your browser, the cookie terminates. If you reject the cookie, you may still use our website. The only drawback to rejecting the cookie is that you may be limited in some areas of our website, such as the ability to retain items in your shopping cart after navigating away from our site. Our website advertises with various other search engines and companies that utilize tracking information on our website to provide us with statistics on the usage of the advertising.
This tracking information is not linked to personally identifiable information.
We may also use IP addresses for analyzing trends, administering the website, tracking user’s movement, and gathering broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.PartnersWe use an outside shipping company to ship orders and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.Newsletters & Special OffersWhen you place an order with us, you are provided the opportunity to subscribe to our newsletter and to receive special offers as they become available, sent to the email address you have provided.
You may also subscribe to our newsletter and to receive special offers without placing an order by providing us with your email address in the area marked “Join our mailing lists” on our home page.Email to a FriendIf you use our referral program to inform a friend about our website, we ask you for the friend’s name and email address. Minimus will automatically send the friend a one-time email containing the information that you requested to be sent and a link to our website.
Minimus stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time per request email.SecurityYour personally identifiable information is kept secure both online and offline. When our registration/order form asks you to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) that information is encrypted and is encrypted using SSL security.
To verify our security or for more information regarding how SSL encrypts and secures your personally identifiable information, click on the Thawte certificate seal at the bottom of our home page.
Offline, visitor and customer information is accessible only by authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential).Fraud Prevention & InvestigationsWe may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.Making Changes to Your Personal InformationIf you have an account with us, you may access it online anytime to update your personal information.
You may also contact us directly using the contact information provided at the bottom of the page.Minimus.biz General Data Protection Regulation [GDPR]
Policy
GDPR is a regulation in European Union (EU) law on data protection and privacy for individuals within the EU and the European Economic Area (EEA). This policy was created to support our compliance with the law and applies to all EU/EEA Client’s customers.
Our Role
Minimus sells and ships products to consumers who purchase from our website (www.minimus.biz), markets to consumers who specifically requested information and provides customer service functions regarding orders/shipments.
Your Data
We market only our company (Minimus.biz) to our customers, or those who have specifically provided their email address, via e-newsletters. Data that is needed to facilitate the function of purchasing and delivery is collected. Data is not purchased from 3rd Party Sources for marketing use. Data is never sold or shared with outside entities. Data captured/ stored includes:
For Purchases:
Purchaser Name, Address, City, State, Zip/Postal, Country, Phone, Email, Payment information (Credit Card), IP address.
For Shipments:
Receiver Name, Address, City, State, Zip/Postal, Country.
For Customer Service:
Email Address
For Marketing:
Name, Email
Customer Information Rights
Minimus customers can easily access and update their personal information to keep it accurate by managing the data in the “YOUR ACCOUNT” section of the website.
Minimus customers can easily request the deletion of their personal data from our order systems, which includes purchase and sales history, from our systems by contacting us via email.
Customers may unsubscribe from our e-newsletter at any time from the link within the e-newsletter.
You may opt-in/ opt-out of marketing at any time in the “YOUR ACCOUNT” section of the website.Opt-In/Opt-OutYou may opt-out of receiving newsletters and other offers by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our newsletters and special offer emails or by contacting us directly using the information provided below.
You may opt-in to newsletters and other special offers by checking the box at the end of your checkout page or by using the subscribe link located on our websites home page.Privacy Contact informationIf you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
By E-Mail:
By Phone: 805-480-1415We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
